Capture:FRS@Evelyn~zx 同步:FRS@观海卫 翻译:某金山快译男
校对：无伤小子 iTunes：Tearemix 双语合成 Lv&daisy
以下内容为电视台提示:
本集中所有角色与情节--即使真实--都是虚构的.
所有名人的声音都是模仿的--很业余
接下来的内容涉及粗话 有鉴于此
所有人都不应该观看
♪ I'm going down to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Going down to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting "howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ Headed on up to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park ♪
♪ And meet some friends of mine ♪
幻想大陆曾经是片充满欢笑的乐土...
Imaginationland used to be  a happy place,
不幸的是这里发生了恐怖袭击
but then the terrorists attacked
我们失去了很多同伴
and so many of us were killed.
防卫长墙也垮了
The barrier came down and all the most evil
恶灵们挣脱了长墙的束缚
imaginary characters were unleashed.
现在是我们 决一死战的时刻了
Now our final battle will take place.
恶灵正在向我们进军
The evil characters are marching toward us...
他们想把我们从幻想大陆上抹去
With the intent to wipe us all out.
这肯定十分精彩 HUH?
This is gonna be fun, huh?!
Yeah! Yeah!
我们正在准备一场不可能成功的战争
We prepare for a battle we cannot win.
那些可爱的童话人物
Sweet and cuddly imaginary characters,
尽管他们当中的许多从未碰过武器
many who have never held a weapon,
也被迫为生存而战
must now fight for their very lives.
我们在数量上不占优势
We are too few in number,
可我们还是有希望
but we have one hope.
这就是你来这的原因,年轻人
That is where you come in, young boy.
只有你才能帮助我们取胜
Only you can help us win this battle.
可是我能做什么呢?
What can I do?
你有着一种神奇的力量 可你现在还没有认识到
You have a power here that you have yet to understand.
幻想大陆之战
第三集
Ahh... Ah!
Ahh!
No!
往回倒一点
Back it up.
看! 就是这个!
Look, right there!
看见了吗?
See that?
No!
这像是什么?
What does that look like to you?
人熊猪...
It's Manbearpig!
我早就警告你们要小心它
I told you it was real!
再看一遍.这就是它确实存在的证据!
Look again.
Ahh!
这个
There!
一半是人 一半是熊,还有一部分是猪!
Half man,half bear, and half pig.
你们看到了吗?
Do you see it?
是的,我们看到了,戈尔先生
Yes, we see it,Mr. Gore.
肯定将会有什么大事情发生,
Something big is going on,
美利坚人民有权知道会发生些什么!
and the American people need to know what.
我不干了!
I'm off!
Wowowoshshhsshh!
他恢复的很快,不过好像有轻微的脑震荡
He's recovering, but there's been some trauma to his brain.
这孩子说他听到了另一个世界传来的声音
The boy says he's been hearing imaginary voices.
Hello?
哈罗?有人吗?
Hello-- anybody?
Stan?
Hello?
早上好啊,KYLE.
Good morning, Kyle.
- 感觉好些了吗? - CARTMAN,发生了什么?
- How are we feeling? - Cartman, what's happened?
发生了什么..?
"What's happened?"
好,我想想.
Well, let's see.
你和我打赌我是否能找到妖精
You bet me that I couldn't prove leprechauns were real,
如果我找到了,
and if I could prove it,
那么你就要吸我老二...我觉得就是这些了.
you had to suck my balls,I believe.
滚,我是问五角大楼里发生了什么!
No, I mean what happened at the Pentagon?
放轻松,KYLE.
You just rest, Kyle.
看我专门为你做的...
Look what I made for you.
圣代!
A sundae.
它是由热巧克力,奶油做成的.
It has hot fudge and whipped cream
和草莓
and a cherry.
我总觉得少了点什么,不是吗,KYLE?
But I feel like something is missing, don't you, Kyle?
圣代到底少了什么..
What else belongs on a sundae
除了巧克力和奶油...
besides hot fudge and whipped cream, hmm...
巧克力 奶油
Ugh!
巧克力  奶油
Hot fudge, whipped cream--
圣代上还少了什么?
what else belongs on a sundae, Kyle?
圣代上少了什么?
What else goes on a sundae
除了巧克力  奶油...
besides hot fudge,whipped cream and...
哦,对了嘛..
Oh, that's right.
我的老二!
My balls.
CARTMAN,到底发生了什么?
Cartman, what is going on out there?
STAN现在怎么样了?
What happened to Stan?
哦,他掉进了那个通道里
Oh, he got sucked through that portal thing
他们现在在...
and they're gonna nuke it now.
你准备好拍特写照片了吗,KYLE?
So are you all set for your big photo shoot, Kyle?
你...你什么意思?STAN现在有危险?!
Wait, what do you mean?Stan's in danger?
别转移话题了,KYLE.
Don't try to change the subject, Kyle.
你为了逃避后果
You've done a really good job
做的还不错.
of trying to get out of this bet,
不过现在也该是做个了结的时候了.
but it's finally time to settle.
准备好好享受圣代吧, KYLE.
Get ready for your sundae, Kyle...
还有特别的坚果哦.
With extra nuts.
ASLAN,恶灵已经在城下聚集了.
Aslan, the evil characters are almost here.
通知所有人准备战斗.
Get everyone to the battlefield.
保卫城墙
Defend the castle walls.
年轻人,快,我们急需你的力量.
Quickly, young boy,we need your powers now.
什么力量?
What powers?
我根本不懂啊.
I don't understand.
你是现实中的人类.
You are real.
是个造物者.
You are a creator.
你想像的东西在这可以变为现实.
That means you can imagine things into existence here.
真的吗?
I-- I can?
圣诞老人在恐怖袭击时已经阵亡,
Santa Claus was killed in the terrorist attack.
你的首要任务就是把他找回来.
The first thing we need is for you to bring him back.
什么?
How?
你只要集中注意力
You just have to focus your mind.
想圣诞老人就可以了.
Imagine Santa and nothing else.
我在这鬼地方怎么能集中注意力呢?
How am I supposed to focus with all this crap going on?
就一件事情
Think only of one thing.
想就可以了.相信自己.
Imagine it,believe in it.
你最经常想的事情就会成真.
Whatever is most prominent in your mind will come to be.
BUTTERS!你被关禁闭了,KYLE.
Butters, you are grounded, mister!
明白了吗?
You hear me?
禁闭!
Grounded!
Agh!
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我们需要的是圣诞老人!
We need Santa!
我在努力啊...
I'm trying!
小孩,想圣诞老人.
Come on, kid,imagine Santa!
想圣诞老人,想圣诞老人
Believe in Santa!
相信圣诞老人
You must believe in Santa!
想圣诞老人,你给我快点!
Believe in Santa right now!
DAH, DAH, DAHHH.
Gah-ha!
♪ Dah-dah-dah dah-dah-dah ♪
♪ Da-di-da ♪
KEVININ,可以把景放开一点吗?
Kevin, can I get some more bounce off that 2-k?
我想用5.6的曝光率,8号镜头.
Let's just go with a 5/6, 8 split.
CARTMAN, 你他妈就不能闭嘴吗?
Cartman,will you shut up?
我正在想发生了什么.
I'm trying to find out what's going on.
新的恐怖袭击似乎即将...
A new terrorist attack seems to have taken place,
发生在我们的幻想世界里...
this time in our imagination.
戈尔公布了这盘录像带
Al Gore brought this video to the public's attention,
为了引起了许多人的关注
sparking demands by everyone
我们原本是准备将其公之于众
who wants to know exactly what's going on.
当然是在此事平息以后.
We were hoping to keep this quiet until it was all over,
不过2天前恐怖分子袭击了
but two days ago there was
我们的童话世界.
a terrorist attack on our imagination,
现在我们的童话已经乱了套.
and now our imaginations are running wild.
童话世界已经乱套了 可是我们居然还不知道?!
Our imaginations are running wild and we weren't told?!
袭击我们的童话世界...
By attacking our imagination
看来恐怖分子找到了我们最软弱的地方
the terrorists have found our most vulnerable spot,
.
我们决定最好的解决办法是...
and we've determined that the best course of action
对童话世界 发动核攻击.
is to nuke our imagination.
核攻击经过了仔细考虑研究吗?
Is nuking our imagination really prudent?
难道没有别的办法
Aren't there other,more peaceful ways
可以和平解决这个问题吗?
to get our imagination under control?
也许我们可以把KURT RUSSELL通过一个特殊通道,
Couldn't we try sending Kurt Russell into a portal
把他送到那个世界,因为...
to our imagination to try and reason with the--
我们已经这样做了.
We tried that,
KURT RUSSELL已经被圣诞小动物鸡奸了.
and Kurt Russell was raped by Christmas Critters!
Ouch.
五角大楼发表声明,
The Pentagon claims that because imaginary things
因为那个世界并不是真实存在的
are not real,
所以准备通过核手段来解决这个问题.
the military doesn't need senate approval to nuke them.
那帮人都是狗屎!
That's bullcrap, man!
不能摧毁我们的童话世界.
You can't nuke our imagination!
我们的童话世界绝对不能被摧毁,兄弟们.
Don't nuke our imagination, bro!
Woo!
MIKE,军方有发动核攻击的权利吗?
Mike, does the military have the authority
攻击我们的童话世界
to nuke our imagination?
很清楚,没有,STEPHEN.
Uh, clearly they don't, Stephen,
因为还有一个很重要的问题没有解决
and they're gonna have a big problem
因为政府已经立法,该法律上指出
because state government has already set a precedent
那些角色都是真实的.
that imaginary characters are real.
原因来自一个叫CARTMAN V. BROFLOVSKI的人
I cite a famous court case of Cartman v. Broflovski
她在法庭上作证,称自己
in which a U.S. Court found for the plaintiff
亲眼见过妖精.
who saw a leprechaun.
真荒唐我觉得那些辩护人
Yes, I believe the defendant
真应该舔老二去了!
had to suck the plaintiff's balls in that case.
没错,STEPHEN.
That's right, Stephen,yeah.
妈的尽鸡巴扯蛋...
Oh, for the love of God!
Hello?
有人能听到吗?
Can anybody hear me?
STAN,
Stan?
是你吗?
Dude, is that you?
KYLE,你在哪?
Kyle?Where are you?
我没看到你.
I don't see you.
我不在你那,我在医院里.
No, I'm not there,I'm in a hospital.
你在我脑海里.
I'm hearing you in my imagination.
OH,那主要会有什么帮助.
Oh, that makes sense.
嘿,到底发生了什么?
Dude, what's happening?
我好像在个什么橡皮糖森林里...
I'm in, like,a gumdrop forest.
我刚看到草莓小蛋糕,她的眼睛被挖了,
I just saw Strawberry Shortcake tied up and dead
眼眶里还被灌了尿.
with pee in her eye.
嘿,等等.
Wait, hang on.
我觉得将要有什么大事情发生.
I think something really big is about to go down.
恶灵已经开始进攻了..?
The evil characters are here!
他们人太多了.
Defend Castle Sunshine.
Hagh!
Hi-yah!
没时间磨蹭了
There's no time left.
你需要控制自己的思想,
You have to get control of your imagination
然后让圣诞老人复活.
and bring Santa back now!
圣诞老人...圣诞老人...
Santa... Santa...
仔细想.
Think!
在脑海中想圣诞老人的形象.红衣服,白胡子.
Jolly old Santa:red suit, white beard!
红衣服,白胡子.
Red suit, white beard...
圣诞老人!
Santa!
Blaryagh!
Agh!
调试的差不多了吗?
How does that look?
可以把圣代和我的老二一起照进去吗?
Can you see my balls and the sundae in frame?
对童话世界发动核攻击的事情有了新的进展
A shocking new development in the nuking of imagination.
最高法院已经向军方授权,
The supreme court has ruled with the military
由于童话并不是真实的
that imaginary things are officially not real
所以发动核攻击不需要得到授权.
and therefore no approval is needed to nuke them.
谢谢!
Thank you.
天啊...
Oh, no.
这显然会推翻许多已经既定的事实
This, of course, overturns
当然也包括了一些比如
any imagination-based verdicts in the past,
著名的
including the famous
两名小男孩互相搞基的事
Cartman v. Broflovski
ball-sucking case.
什么?!
What?
现在军方
So it appears the military
即将发动核攻击.
is ready to proceed with its operation,
该行动的代号是:
one they are calling:
"通过幻想大陆通道对幻想大陆发动核攻击"
Operation Nuke the Imagination Through the Imagination Doorway.
KYLE 怎么了?
Kyle, what's happening?
政府要用核武器把幻想大陆给炸了
The government is gonna nuke Imaginationland.
什么?!
What?!
你要阻止他们这样啊..
You can't let them do that!
那我该怎么办?
What am I supposed to do?
你要让他们取消这个计划啊!
Dude, you have to stall them!
OH, OH, 那是什么?
Oh, uh-oh,what is that?!
HEY! 走开!
Hey, get outta here!
离我远点!
Leave me alone!
Stan... Stan?
你他妈的要去哪?!
Where are you going?
我要去救BUTTERS和TAN
I'm going to try and save Stan and Butters
- 免遭核打击 - 好
- from getting nuked. - Okay, okay.
不过你要先舔我老二.
But you have to suck my balls first real quick.
我才不呢!
No I don't!
判决可是改了的!
The decision was overturned!
我们可是有协议的, KYLE!
We had a deal, Kyle!
是,妖精确实存在,
Yeah, that leprechauns were real,
政府只说他们存在,
and the government just declared
不过还没有事实证明.
they aren't technically real, so I was right!
我也不用舔你老二了.
I don't have to suck your balls!
这事没完!
It isn't over!
这事才没完呢, KYLE.
It isn't over,Kyle!
我等待这一刻那么久,
I have not waited this long
你一直在逃避舔我老二的责任.
to see you weasel your way out of this bet!
走...你走吧...不过我以生命发誓,
Go ahead and go,but I swear on my life,
在太阳落山之前,
before this day is over,
你绝对要舔我老二!
you will suck my balls.
我发誓!
I swear it!
YEAH,我觉得马上就要结束了.
Yeah, it's gets me strong to the finish...
POPEYE 我们需要更多菠菜
We need more spinach for Popeye.
Ugh!
Ooh!
我干掉了一个!干掉了一个!
I got one,I got him!
HEY,你好啊.
Hey there!- Huh?
Yay!
战况好像对我们不利!
We're losing the battle!
他们人数实在是太多了!
There are simply too many of them!
毁灭的时刻就要到了.
Then the day is lost...
等等! ASLAN,看!
Wait, Aslan, look!
孩子,你坐到了!
You did it, kid!
圣诞老人,快,他们需要你去战斗!
Quickly, Santa, they need you on the battlefield.
Huh?
呃...好吧!
Oh, all right.
就看我圣诞老人的吧!
Make way for Santa!
Ugh!
Hugh!
现在知道自己的能力了吧,年轻的造物主.
Now you see your potential,young creator.
不过如果要赢,
But there is still much more we need from you
你还有更多的需要去做.
if we are to win this day.
这是禁区,小孩.
This area is restricted,little boy!
求你了,我要和里面的人谈谈.
Please, I need to talk to the people inside.
他们不能发动核攻击!
They can't set off that nuke.
退到线外去,像那些示威者一样!
Get behind the line with the other protesters.
不能发动核攻击,兄弟们.
No nukes in out imagination, bro!
Whoo! Whoo!
你们什么都不知道..
You don't understand.
我朋友就在幻想大陆里!
My friend is in Imaginationland.
我能听到他和我说话!
I can hear him in my head.
一帮专门抽大麻的嬉皮士,你们可不能进去!
You pot-smoking hippies aren't getting through here,
你他妈滚开!
so back off!
不要核攻击!
Stop that nuke!
这是发生了什么啊?
What's going on here?
军方的做法是对的,
The military has to do this.
不这样做的话没法消灭人熊猪.
It's their only way to kill Manbearpig!
Wowowoshshhsshh!
干得好,BUTTERS!
Good, Butters.
多想像几个弓箭手!
Now imagine some more archers on the castle walls.
Hughgh!
ASLAN,战况不妙啊...
Aslan, we are losing the battle!
我们成功击退了那些吸血鬼,
We managed to fight off the vampires and werewolves
不过我们对那些.
but now our troops are being shot down
口腔细菌毫无办法
by the Cavity Creeps!
口腔细菌..?
Cavity Creeps?
我们在牙齿上打洞!
We make holes in teeth!
那什么才能没有蛀牙呢?
What can destroy the Cavity Creeps?
只有佳洁士能办到.
Only Crest Gel with Tartar Control.
快!想像一支大号的佳洁士牙膏!
Quickly, you must imagine a giant Crest Gel.
Yes!
他的力量越来越强大了.
His powers are getting stronger.
也许我们有机会赢!
We might just have a chance here.
是在橡皮糖森林 巡逻时发现的
He was sneaking around the Gumdrop Forest.
Stan!
HEY,看,我创造了STAN!
Hey, look,I imagined Stan here!
不,不.
No, no!
我是被"通往幻想大陆的通道的计划"给吸进来的 五角大楼里的那个
I got sucked through Project Imagination Doorway at the Pentagon.
"通往幻想大陆的通道的计划"..?
Project Imagination Doorway?
不用管
Nevermind.
我们即将获胜!
The battle is almost won.
等胜利了以后再处理他也不迟.
We can deal with him later.
不对,不对,你们还不了解情况
No, no,
you don't understand.
将会有核攻击
There's a nuke.
政府要把幻想大陆给彻底摧毁!
The government is about to level this entire place.
什么?!
What?
为什么要炸幻想大陆?
Why would they nuke Imaginationland?
这样的话恐怖分子再也不能对这里发动袭击了.
So the terrorists can't ever use it against us again.
我们可以恢复幻想大陆的秩序.
We can get Imaginationland under control!
有这位造物主很快就可以了!
The chosen one just needs more time!
造物主..?
The chosen one?
YEAH,似乎我是这里的关键先生.
Yeah, it turns out I'm the key.
核攻击即将发动...
Missile launch sequence initiated.
大家都听好了 我要将这次行动写成一本书.
All right, people, I want this nuking done by the books.
长官,有个安全警报.
Sir, we have a security breach.
啊
What?!
在2区.
It's coming from sector two!
2区..?
Sector two?
Gah!
你他妈的到底在干什么?
What the hell do think you're doing,
赶快发表声明,妖精是真的!
declaring leprechauns aren't real?!
什么?
What?
你们刚说那妖精是假的,不存在的.
You just can't declare that imaginary things aren't real.
不过你有什么权利说他们是假的?!
Who are you to say what's real?
好好想想,
Think about it.
色情是真实的吗?爱情是真实的吗?
Is blue real? Is love really real?
那些都是人们想像出来的.
Imaginary things are things made up by people,
就像圣诞老人,鲁多夫一样.
like Santa and Rudolph.
对,也有的是改编自真实事例..
Yeah, and they detract from real things.
比如耶稣.
Like Jesus.
说不定耶稣也是纯粹编出来的.
Maybe Jesus is imaginary too.
最好不要这样说噢.
Ooh, you better not say that.
不然要下地狱的.
You'll go to Hell.
很有可能地狱也是幻想出来的.
It's possible that Hell is also imaginary.
所以...我们把地狱一起给炸了!
So then we're about to nuke Hell.
这算干了件好事,不是吗?
That's a good thing, right?
对!对!那可是件好事!对.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. That's good, that's a good thing, yeah.
不过如果天堂也是想像中的?
What if Heaven is imaginary?
我们把天堂也给炸了...
We'd be nuking Heaven.
对,不过天堂不是真的.
Yeah, but it wouldn't be real.
那就这么干了吧.
So it'd be all right.
也许这些都是一样的.
Look, maybe they're all part of the same thing--
圣诞老人,耶稣 还有妖精们
Santa and Jesus and Hell and leprechauns.
在某种程度上说他们都是真实存在的 不是吗?
Maybe they're all real in the same way, right?
圣诞老人和妖精是假的,
Santa Claus and leprechauns are imaginary
不过耶稣和地狱是真的!
but Jesus and Hell are real.
恩,那么佛呢?
Well, then what about Buddha?
当然了,那是假的!
Well, of course he's imaginary!
我是真实的吗?
Am I real?
好了,都够了!
All right, enough!
别管那小屁孩,
Keep that kid out of our way
都回到自己的岗位上,准备核攻击!
and let's get back to the nuking at hand!
Kyle?
KYLE,事情有进展吗?
Kyle, what happened?
没有.
Nothing.
什么?
What?
没有任何进展. 我什么都干不了.
Nothing happened--there's nothing I can do.
兄弟,你可不能让政府
Dude, you can't let the government
发射核弹啊!
fire off that nuke.
他们说这事随便怎么都行,
They say they can do whatever they want
因为那些都不是真的.
because imaginary things aren't real.
那你就去说服他们这些都是真的!
Well, you have to convince them they are real.
嘿,那这样我不是要去
No way, dude.
舔CARTMAN的老二了吗?
Then I'd have to suck Cartman's balls.
不管有多大的困难,你都要克服,明白了吗?
Whatever it takes, you have to do it, all right?
等等,Kyle.
Hang-- hang on, Kyle.
耶稣要和你说两句.
Jesus wants to talk to you.
HUH?
听到了吗,KYLE 我是耶稣.
Hello,Kyle, this is Jesus.
天啊...
Oh, boy.
有什么问题吗,我的孩子?
What seems to be the problem, my child?
耶稣,我什么也做不了啊.
Jesus, I can't do anything!
我只是个决议的抗议者.
I'm just a fourth-grader
针对整个政府
going against the entire government!
哈罗?耶稣？
Hello... Jesus?
我是天行者.
No,this is skywalker.
Ugh!
我知道这是个很艰难的任务,
Look, I know this seems like an impossible task,
不过你还记得我是怎么摧毁死星的吗?
but you remember when I brought down the Death Star?
我的意思是,那也同样很艰难,不是吗?
I mean, that seemed impossible too, right?
YEAH,可以算是吧.
Yeah, I guess.
他想说点啥
and he wants to say something.
KYLE,我是超人.
Kyle, this is Superman.
你好,超人...
Hi, Superman.
我了解,拯救别人是个很重的责任
I know that saving people can be a big responsibility,
不过无论代价怎样,他都是值得的
but no matter what it takes,it's worth it.
我知道.
I know.
你能做到的,KYLE?
You can do this, Kyle.
别挂,赫克琉斯也要和你说两句.
Now hang on, because Hercules wants to talk to you.
上帝啊..!
Oh, God.
恩,上帝也在这呢,
Yes, God is here too.
克劳奇船长之后就轮到他了.
He's gonna talk to you right after Captain Crunch.
Agh... Agh!
大力水手,来帮帮我啊!
Popeye, I need some help here!
大力水手已经被圣诞小动物给制服了
Popeye is being killed by Christmas Critters!
.
Ahghgh!
UGHGH,给...给...给我...滚...滚开点...
Ughgh--Gets 'em off a me!
HEY,那是什么?
Hey, what is that?
给大力水手一车菠菜!
More spinach for Popeye!
给耶稣一把M-60机枪!
Imagine a M-60 for Jesus!
太爽了!
All right!
那孩子正在改变战局.
The boy is doing it!
看来幻想大陆又要恢复秩序了.
Everything is going to be okay!
距导弹发射一分钟.
Missile launch in one minute.
操你妈的!
Goddamn it!
你们这群傻逼知道自己在干什么吗?
You stupid assholes are gonna ruin everything!
准备发射.
Prepare for launch.
长官,有个安全警报.
Sir, we have a security breach!
什么?
What?!
是非法入侵警报.
There's an unauthorized entry alert.
在2区.
It's coming from sector two!
2区?
Sector two?
KYLE?
你他妈在那后面干什么?
What the hell are you doing back here?
听着,你们不用这样做了!
Listen, you don't have to do this.
幻想大陆已经回到原来的秩序下了
Our imaginations aren't running wild any more!
.
这是为什么,
Why is it so easy for children
一个孩子能这样容易的闯入五角大楼?
to break into the Pentagon?
你必须停下来.
You have to stop!
如果我没记错的话...
If I'm not mistaken,you're the one who bet
你可一直不相信妖精是真的,
that leprechauns weren't real.
那你又关心这事干什么呢?
So why do you care what happens?
因为我,因为我觉得...
Because I, I...
他们确实是真的.
Um, because I think they are real.
都是存在的
It's all real.
大家想想,
Think about it.
圣诞老人或天行者
Haven't Luke Skywalker and Santa Claus
对你的影响
affected your lives
比这个房间里的所有人对你的影响都要大的多
more than most real people in this room?
我的意思是,不管耶稣他是真是假
I mean, whether Jesus is real or not,
他对这个世界的影响
he's had a bigger impact on the world
比我们任何人的影响都要大
than any of us have.
BUNNY的影响也很大
And the same can be said for Bugs Bunny
还有超人和哈利波特.
and Superman and Harry Potter.
他们改变了我的生活.
They've changed my life,
改变了我处事的方式.
changed the way I act on the earth.
难道这不算对我们真实的影响吗?
Doesn't that make them kind of real?
他们虽然是虚构的,
They might be imaginary,
不过却比我们更加重要.
but they're more important than most of us here...
在我们死后 他们对后人的影响仍然那么大.
And they're all gonna be around long after we're dead.
所以从某种意义上来说,
So in a way...
他们比我们更加的真实.
Those things are more realer than any of us.
放弃发射.
Abort the sequence.
所以,那些幻想确实都是真的,不是吗
So, Kyle, imaginary things are real, huh?
所以这证明了 最后我还是赢了
Guess that means I did win the bet after all.
KYLE.你应该也这样觉得吧.
And you know what that means, Kyle.
把你的蛋蛋给收起来吧,
Just let it go with your fucking balls already,
你个傻逼鸡巴!
you fucking asshole!
朋友身处险境,
Your friends have been in danger
你却只关心打赌的事.
and all you care about is this stupid bet.
好,我决定了, CARTMAN,就算我们的确打了那个赌
Well, I've decided,Cartman, even if we had a bet,
我也绝不会吸你老二,
that I am never sucking your balls!
知道了吗?!
You got that?!
你可以把我关进监狱里渡过余生,
They can throw me in jail for the rest of my life
不过我绝对不会吸你老二了!
but I am never going to suck your balls ever!
怎么了?
What happened?!
核弹为什么没有发射?
Why hasn't the missile gone off?!
计划已经取消了,戈尔先生.
There's been an abort Mr. Gore.
不行,
No!
人熊猪必须要死!
Manbearpig has to die!
天啊,停下来!
Oh, Jesus, no!
Hahgghgh!
结束了,ASLAN!
That's it, Aslan!
恶灵们都被消灭了.
The evil characters have fled!
胜利是我们的!
The day is ours!
Agh! Agh!
Kyle!
嘿,你们怎么也来了?
Fellas, where'd you come from?
那是什么?
What is that?
Huh...
他又做到了!
He did it!
看啊!我复活了!
Oh, look,I'm back!
好样的,孩子!
Nice going, kid!
干得不错！Butters!
Great job! - Yeah! - All right,
- Butters!
那些恶灵...
The evil characters!
他们回到长墙那边去了!
They're all back behind the wall again!
你是怎么做到的,
Dude, how did you do that, Butters?
我就是专心想!
I just...Used my imagination!
Aww! Aww!
我从你们身上学到了很多.
You know, I really have learned a lot, you guys.
像KYLE说的,那些虚构任务 其实有着真实的影响
What Kyle said about imaginary things being real,
还有BUTTERS如何利用 自己的想像力
and Butters using his imagination,
其实我觉得,恩,
it makes me think that--
也许每个人都能
Well, maybe we all have the power
利用自己的想象力
to make things a reality.
看啊,是我.
Oh, why, look,it's me!
然后,
And...
那是KYLE!
And there's Kyle!
KYLE在做什么呢?
And what's Kyle about to do?
CARTMAN,别这样...
Cartman, don't.
Oh, Kyle!
KYLE!你对我老二干什么呢?
What are you doing to my balls?
OH, OH.看啊,
Oh-ho, look!
KYLE在吸我老二!
It's Kyle sucking my balls!
喂...
Dude.
上帝！
Oh, my God!
KYLE,你果然对老二很饥渴啊...
Oh, Kyle, you are gobbling those balls, aren't you?
我告诉过你了,在这事结束之前,
I told you you would suck my balls before this was over,
我们还是会有个了断的.
didn't I, Kyle?
我才没吸你老二呢!
I'm not sucking your balls.
那是你想像出来的!
That's imaginary!
才不呢,KYLE,我记得你说过
No, Kyle,I believe you said
想像中的也算是真实的
that imaginary things are real.
没错,你是这样说的.
That's true, you did!
看看你在干什么,KYLE.
Oh, look at you go, Kyle!
真是个不爱干净的娘们.
Oh, you dirty girl.
看来你很喜欢老二嘛!
You love those balls!
好了,这事差不多够了...
Okay, Kyle,that's enough ball-sucking.
该把你们送回家了.
We need to get you boys home.
我才没吸CARTMAN的老二呢!
I am not sucking Cartman's balls!
只要相信,终究能梦想成真!
Whatever you imagine to be real is real!
Woo-hoo! Woo-hoo!
Butters... Butters!
Huh?!
什么?
What?
Oh...
到底这还是个梦...
Oh, it was all just a dream.
快点吧,BUTTERS,该起床了.
Come on, Butters,time to get up.
爸爸!我做了个疯狂的梦,
Oh, Dad,I had the craziest dream.
我一个人拯救了幻想大陆!
I saved all of Imaginationland from running wild
还躲过了恐怖分子的袭击!
after a terrorist attack!
你确实去了趟幻想大陆,BUTTERS!
You were in Imaginationland, Butters!
我们从报纸上都知道了.
We've read all about it in the paper.
不过问题是
The question is:
当你在幻想大陆的时候
what were you doing in Imaginationland
本应该是帮妈妈
when you were supposed to be helping your mother
打扫地下室的!
clean up the basement?
你被关禁闭了!
You are grounded,mister!
Aww.
等等,我没被关禁闭.
Wait, I'm not grounded.
你确实是要被关了!
Oh, yes, you are!
真的吗..?
Oh, yeah?
那土逼办法只在幻想大陆才行得通
That only works in Imaginationland.
你被关了!
You're grounded!
一砣屎!
Aw, shit.
welcome to www.1000fr.com